<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv source-info-url="https://github.com/your-repo" source-info-name="NFL EPG">
  <channel id="NFL01">
    <display-name>NFL 01</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL02">
    <display-name>NFL 02</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL03">
    <display-name>NFL 03</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL04">
    <display-name>NFL 04</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL05">
    <display-name>NFL 05</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL06">
    <display-name>NFL 06</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL07">
    <display-name>NFL 07</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL08">
    <display-name>NFL 08</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL09">
    <display-name>NFL 09</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL10">
    <display-name>NFL 10</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL11">
    <display-name>NFL 11</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL12">
    <display-name>NFL 12</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL13">
    <display-name>NFL 13</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL14">
    <display-name>NFL 14</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL15">
    <display-name>NFL 15</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL16">
    <display-name>NFL 16</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL17">
    <display-name>NFL 17</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL18">
    <display-name>NFL 18</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL19">
    <display-name>NFL 19</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL20">
    <display-name>NFL 20</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL21">
    <display-name>NFL 21</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL22">
    <display-name>NFL 22</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL23">
    <display-name>NFL 23</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL24">
    <display-name>NFL 24</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL25">
    <display-name>NFL 25</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL26">
    <display-name>NFL 26</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL27">
    <display-name>NFL 27</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL28">
    <display-name>NFL 28</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL29">
    <display-name>NFL 29</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL30">
    <display-name>NFL 30</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251019122500 +0000" stop="20251019132500 +0000" channel="NFL01">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Rams vs Jaguars</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for an epic showdown as the Los Angeles Rams take on the Jacksonville Jaguars in a battle of two powerhouse teams. The Rams, led by star quarterback Matthew Stafford and defensive powerhouse Aaron Donald, boast an impressive record of 10-3 and are currently sitting at the top of the NFC West. On the other side, the Jaguars, led by dynamic rookie quarterback Trevor Lawrence and defensive standout Josh Allen, are looking to make a statement with their 8-5 record and a strong push for a playoff spot in the AFC South.

Both teams are coming off impressive wins and are hungry for a victory in this crucial matchup that could have huge playoff implications for both teams. With the Rams looking to solidify their position at the top of the NFC and</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019132500 +0000" stop="20251019162500 +0000" channel="NFL01">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Rams at Jaguars - 9:25 AM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to the thrilling NFL game between the Los Angeles Rams and the Jacksonville Jaguars! We are currently in the third quarter, with the Rams leading 21-14.

The Rams got off to a strong start with a touchdown pass from Matthew Stafford to Cooper Kupp, but the Jaguars quickly answered back with a touchdown of their own thanks to a long run by James Robinson. However, the Rams have been able to capitalize on turnovers, with a key interception by Jalen Ramsey leading to another touchdown for the Rams.

Both teams have been making big plays on both sides of the ball, with standout performances from Aaron Donald on the Rams' defense and Trevor Lawrence leading the Jaguars' offense. The Rams have been able to capitalize on turnovers and have been able to</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019162500 +0000" stop="20251019172500 +0000" channel="NFL01">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Rams vs Jaguars</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a highly anticipated matchup between the Los Angeles Rams and the Jacksonville Jaguars, the Rams emerged victorious with a final score of 31-17. The game was closely contested throughout, but the Rams were able to pull away in the second half with a strong offensive performance.

Key moments in the game included a 60-yard touchdown pass from Rams quarterback Matthew Stafford to wide receiver Cooper Kupp, as well as a crucial interception by Rams cornerback Jalen Ramsey late in the fourth quarter. Both plays swung the momentum in favor of the Rams and ultimately helped secure the win.

Player performances were highlighted by Stafford's impressive passing game, finishing with 300+ passing yards and multiple touchdowns. Kupp also had a standout game with over 100 receiving yards and a</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019155500 +0000" stop="20251019165500 +0000" channel="NFL02">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Panthers vs Jets</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for a showdown on the gridiron as the Carolina Panthers take on the New York Jets in what promises to be a thrilling NFL game. The Panthers, led by star quarterback Sam Darnold, are currently sitting at a solid 7-4 record and are hungry for a win to solidify their playoff hopes. Meanwhile, the Jets, with rookie sensation Zach Wilson at the helm, are looking to play spoiler and upset the Panthers with their unpredictable play.

Both teams have shown flashes of brilliance in recent weeks, with the Panthers coming off a dominant win against the Dolphins and the Jets shocking the league with an upset over the Titans. With playoff implications on the line for the Panthers and the Jets playing with nothing to lose, this game is sure</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019165500 +0000" stop="20251019195500 +0000" channel="NFL02">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Panthers at Jets - 12:55 PM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to the exciting NFL matchup between the Carolina Panthers and New York Jets! We are currently in the third quarter with the Panthers leading 21-10.

The Panthers have been dominating on both sides of the ball, with quarterback Sam Darnold connecting with wide receiver Robby Anderson for two touchdown passes. Running back Christian McCaffrey has also been a force to be reckoned with, racking up over 100 yards rushing and a touchdown.

The Jets have been struggling to find their rhythm, with quarterback Zach Wilson throwing two interceptions in the first half. However, their defense has been putting up a fight, with linebacker C.J. Mosley leading the charge with several key tackles and a forced fumble.

Both teams have been trading blows in</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019195500 +0000" stop="20251019205500 +0000" channel="NFL02">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Panthers vs Jets</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Carolina Panthers faced off against the New York Jets in a thrilling NFL football game that ended with a final score of 27-24 in favor of the Panthers. 

Key moments in the game included a strong start by the Panthers, who jumped out to an early lead with a touchdown pass from quarterback Sam Darnold to wide receiver DJ Moore. The Jets fought back with a touchdown of their own, but the Panthers' defense held strong, forcing turnovers and making key stops to keep them in the lead.

Player performances were highlighted by the outstanding play of Panthers running back Christian McCaffrey, who rushed for over 100 yards and scored two touchdowns. Quarterback Sam Darnold also had a solid game, throwing for over 200 yards and</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019155500 +0000" stop="20251019165500 +0000" channel="NFL03">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Saints vs Bears</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for an epic showdown on the gridiron as the New Orleans Saints take on the Chicago Bears in a must-win game with playoff implications on the line. The Saints, led by superstar quarterback Drew Brees, are currently sitting at the top of the NFC South with a 10-4 record and are looking to secure a spot in the postseason. Meanwhile, the Bears, led by their dominant defense and explosive offense, are fighting to stay alive in the playoff race with a 7-7 record.

Both teams are coming off impressive wins in their previous games and are hungry for victory in this crucial matchup. The Saints will be looking to continue their winning streak and solidify their position in the playoffs, while the Bears will be looking to play</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019165500 +0000" stop="20251019195500 +0000" channel="NFL03">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Saints at Bears - 12:55 PM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to the exciting matchup between the New Orleans Saints and Chicago Bears! We are currently in the third quarter with the Saints leading 21-14.

The game has been filled with big plays and turnovers, with both teams showcasing their offensive firepower. Saints quarterback Jameis Winston has been impressive, throwing for two touchdowns and leading his team down the field with precision passing.

On the other side, Bears quarterback Justin Fields has shown flashes of brilliance, connecting on a deep touchdown pass to Allen Robinson. However, he has also struggled with turnovers, throwing an interception that led to a Saints touchdown.

The Saints defense has been dominant, forcing two turnovers and putting pressure on Fields throughout the game. They have been led by standout performances from defensive end Cameron Jordan and cornerback</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019195500 +0000" stop="20251019205500 +0000" channel="NFL03">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Saints vs Bears</title>
    <desc lang="en">The New Orleans Saints faced off against the Chicago Bears in a highly anticipated NFL matchup. The final score of the game was 24-21, with the Saints coming out on top.

Key moments in the game included a strong start by the Saints, who jumped out to an early lead with a touchdown in the first quarter. The Bears fought back, scoring a touchdown of their own to tie the game in the second quarter. However, the Saints were able to regain the lead before halftime with another touchdown, giving them a slight edge going into the second half.

Player performances were a major factor in the outcome of the game, with Saints quarterback Drew Brees leading the way with two touchdown passes. The Saints defense also played a crucial role, holding the</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019155500 +0000" stop="20251019165500 +0000" channel="NFL05">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Dolphins vs Browns</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for an epic showdown between the Miami Dolphins and Cleveland Browns in a game that is sure to keep you on the edge of your seat! Both teams are hungry for a win as they battle it out on the gridiron.

The Dolphins, led by star quarterback Tua Tagovailoa, are coming off a strong performance with a record of 6-3 and are looking to solidify their playoff position. On the other side, the Browns, led by quarterback Baker Mayfield, are also in the hunt for a playoff spot with a record of 5-4.

Recent performances from both teams have been impressive, with the Dolphins showcasing their strong defense and the Browns displaying their explosive offense. This game is sure to be a high-sc</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019165500 +0000" stop="20251019195500 +0000" channel="NFL05">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Dolphins at Browns - 12:55 PM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to an exciting NFL matchup between the Miami Dolphins and Cleveland Browns! As we enter the second quarter, the Dolphins are leading with a score of 14-7.

The game started off with a bang as the Dolphins' quarterback, Tua Tagovailoa, connected with wide receiver Jaylen Waddle for a 70-yard touchdown pass on the opening drive. The Browns quickly responded with a touchdown of their own, courtesy of a 1-yard run by running back Nick Chubb.

The Dolphins defense has been relentless, forcing two turnovers in the first quarter. Safety Jevon Holland intercepted a pass from Browns quarterback Baker Mayfield, while cornerback Xavien Howard recovered a fumble deep in Browns territory, leading to another Dolphins touchdown.</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019195500 +0000" stop="20251019205500 +0000" channel="NFL05">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Dolphins vs Browns</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Miami Dolphins faced off against the Cleveland Browns in a highly anticipated NFL matchup that ended with a final score of 24-21 in favor of the Dolphins. 

Key moments in the game included a strong start by the Browns, who took an early lead with two quick touchdowns. However, the Dolphins fought back with a solid defensive effort and a stellar performance by their quarterback, Tua Tagovailoa, who threw for over 300 yards and three touchdowns. The Dolphins' defense also came up big with several key turnovers that swung the momentum in their favor.

One of the turning points in the game was a crucial interception by the Dolphins' defense in the fourth quarter, which led to a game-winning touchdown for Miami. This play proved to be</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019155500 +0000" stop="20251019165500 +0000" channel="NFL06">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Raiders vs Chiefs</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for an epic showdown as the Las Vegas Raiders take on the Kansas City Chiefs in a high-stakes AFC West battle. Both teams are sitting at the top of the division with impressive records, making this game crucial for playoff positioning.

The Raiders, led by quarterback Derek Carr and standout tight end Darren Waller, have been on a hot streak recently with key wins over tough opponents. Their dynamic offense and solid defense have propelled them to a winning record and put them in prime position for a playoff run.

On the other side, the Chiefs, led by superstar quarterback Patrick Mahomes and explosive wide receiver Tyreek Hill, are looking to continue their dominance in the division and solidify their playoff chances. With their high-powered offense and stingy defense</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019165500 +0000" stop="20251019195500 +0000" channel="NFL06">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Raiders at Chiefs - 12:55 PM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to the exciting NFL matchup between the Las Vegas Raiders and the Kansas City Chiefs! The game is currently in the second quarter with the Raiders leading 14-10.

The Raiders have been showcasing a strong offensive performance with quarterback Derek Carr connecting with wide receiver Henry Ruggs III for a couple of impressive touchdown passes. Running back Josh Jacobs has also been making some key plays on the ground, picking up crucial first downs for the team.

The Chiefs, on the other hand, have been relying on the arm of quarterback Patrick Mahomes to keep them in the game. Mahomes has been making some incredible throws, including a deep touchdown pass to wide receiver Tyreek Hill.

Both teams have been playing tough defense, with the Raiders managing to force a</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019195500 +0000" stop="20251019205500 +0000" channel="NFL06">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Raiders vs Chiefs</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Las Vegas Raiders faced off against the Kansas City Chiefs in a highly anticipated AFC West showdown. The game was a thrilling back-and-forth battle that ultimately ended with the Raiders pulling off a stunning upset, defeating the Chiefs 40-32.

Key moments in the game included a 72-yard touchdown run by Raiders running back Josh Jacobs, a 59-yard touchdown pass from Chiefs quarterback Patrick Mahomes to Tyreek Hill, and a crucial interception by Raiders safety Jeff Heath in the fourth quarter. Both teams traded blows throughout the game, but it was the Raiders who made the key plays when it mattered most.

Player performances were highlighted by Derek Carr's stellar performance, throwing for 347 yards and three touchdowns. Tight end Darren Waller also had a</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019155500 +0000" stop="20251019165500 +0000" channel="NFL07">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Patriots vs Titans</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for a showdown of titans as the New England Patriots take on the Tennessee Titans in a highly anticipated NFL matchup. Both teams are coming off impressive wins and are eager to continue their momentum.

The Patriots, led by star quarterback Mac Jones and veteran coach Bill Belichick, currently hold a record of 8-4 and are sitting comfortably atop the AFC East. They are known for their resilient defense and explosive offense, making them a force to be reckoned with.

On the other side, the Titans, led by quarterback Ryan Tannehill and running back Derrick Henry, are also having a strong season with a record of 8-4. They have been dominant in the AFC South and are looking to solidify their playoff position with a</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019165500 +0000" stop="20251019195500 +0000" channel="NFL07">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Patriots at Titans - 12:55 PM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to the exciting NFL matchup between the New England Patriots and the Tennessee Titans! As we enter the second quarter, the Patriots are leading 14-7 thanks to a touchdown pass from quarterback Mac Jones to wide receiver Kendrick Bourne.

The Titans started off strong with a touchdown run by Derrick Henry, but the Patriots defense has been able to contain him for the most part. However, Henry just broke through for a 30-yard run to set up a potential scoring opportunity for the Titans.

The Patriots defense has been impressive, forcing a turnover on downs and intercepting Titans quarterback Ryan Tannehill in the red zone. Linebacker Dont'a Hightower has been a standout player with multiple tackles for loss and a key interception.

On the offensive</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019195500 +0000" stop="20251019205500 +0000" channel="NFL07">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Patriots vs Titans</title>
    <desc lang="en">Final Score: Patriots 24, Titans 17

Highlights:
- The Patriots started off strong, with quarterback Mac Jones leading the offense with precision passing and two early touchdown drives.
- The Titans fought back in the second half, with running back Derrick Henry breaking loose for a 50-yard touchdown run and quarterback Ryan Tannehill connecting with wide receiver A.J. Brown for a touchdown.
- The Patriots defense came up big in the fourth quarter, forcing a key turnover on downs to seal the victory.

Key Moments:
- Mac Jones' early touchdown passes set the tone for the game and gave the Patriots an early lead that they were able to hold onto.
- Derrick Henry's long touchdown run energized the Titans and gave them momentum in the second</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019155500 +0000" stop="20251019165500 +0000" channel="NFL08">
    <title lang="en">Pre-Game: Eagles vs Vikings</title>
    <desc lang="en">Get ready for a clash of titans as the Philadelphia Eagles take on the Minnesota Vikings in a highly anticipated NFL showdown! The Eagles, boasting a solid 7-3 record, will be looking to extend their winning streak with star quarterback Jalen Hurts leading the charge. On the other side, the Vikings, sitting at 6-4, will be relying on the arm of Kirk Cousins and the dynamic duo of Dalvin Cook and Justin Jefferson to secure a crucial victory.

Both teams are coming off impressive wins and are hungry for a playoff spot, making this game a must-watch for football fans everywhere. With playoff implications on the line, every play will be crucial in determining the fate of these two talented teams.

So, mark your calendars and</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019165500 +0000" stop="20251019195500 +0000" channel="NFL08">
    <title lang="en">ᴸᶦᵛᵉ Eagles at Vikings - 12:55 PM ET</title>
    <desc lang="en">Welcome to the thrilling NFL matchup between the Philadelphia Eagles and Minnesota Vikings! We are currently in the third quarter with the Eagles leading 17-14.

The game has been a back-and-forth battle with both teams showcasing their offensive firepower. The Eagles struck first with a touchdown pass from Jalen Hurts to DeVonta Smith, but the Vikings quickly answered with a touchdown of their own courtesy of Kirk Cousins connecting with Adam Thielen.

Both teams have been able to move the ball effectively, but turnovers have been a key factor in the game. The Eagles forced a fumble in the second quarter which led to a field goal, while the Vikings intercepted Jalen Hurts in the red zone to halt a potential scoring drive.

One standout player in this</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251019195500 +0000" stop="20251019205500 +0000" channel="NFL08">
    <title lang="en">Post-Game: Eagles vs Vikings</title>
    <desc lang="en">The Philadelphia Eagles faced off against the Minnesota Vikings in a thrilling NFL matchup that ended with a final score of 24-21 in favor of the Vikings. 

Key moments in the game included a standout performance by Vikings quarterback Kirk Cousins, who threw for 236 yards and 2 touchdowns. The Eagles' defense put up a strong fight, but ultimately couldn't contain the Vikings' offense. 

Player performances were highlighted by Vikings running back Dalvin Cook, who rushed for 94 yards and 1 touchdown, as well as Eagles quarterback Jalen Hurts, who threw for 188 yards and 1 touchdown. 

Turning points in the game included a crucial interception by the Vikings' defense in the fourth quarter, which ultimately sealed the win for Minnesota</desc>
    <category>Sports</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>